escortgps.xxx 2017-06-06

# Privacy Statement - Escort GPS Your free Escort Global Directory Search Engine!

Escort GPS is owned and operated by EGPSX, a company committed to respecting your privacy and complying with all applicable data protection and privacy laws. This privacy statement explains the data collection and use practices of the Escort  GPS website.

**Anonymous Access**

You can visit our website without disclosing any personally identifiable information about yourself.

**Personal Information Collection**

We endeavor to collect your personal information only with your knowledge and consent. The type of personal information we may collect could include, for example, your name, email address or telephone number, and situations where we may collect personal information could include, for example, when you register to use specific website services provided by us or contact us. If you choose to provide us with personal information it will be used in support of the intended purposes stated at the time at which it was collected and subject to any preferences indicated by you.

**Non-Personally Identifying Information**

We may also collect non-personally identifying information about your [ebony porn](http://hq-ebony-porn.tumblr.com/) visit to our website, like your IP address and details of your browsing activities within our website.

**How Will We Use Your Information?**

We may use your information for a number of purposes which could include providing website services to you, responding to your inquiries and helping us manage and develop our website.

**When Will We Disclose Your Information To Others?**

We will not pass your personal information to any third parties unless you give us express permission to do so or we are required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us; (b) protect and defend our rights or property; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the safety of anyone.

**Cookies**

We may use cookies for two reasons; to help us track usage patterns in order to improve our website and to record preferences in order to personalise your visit. You should have the ability to accept or decline cookies within your web browser settings. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other websites you visit.

**Access To Personal Information We May Hold About You**

You can ask us at any time whether we are keeping any personal information about you and we will endeavor to respond to you promptly and provide you with a readable copy of any personal information which we are keeping about you. We will also allow you to challenge any personal information that we may hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the information erased or amended. We will need proof of identity before we can discuss with you any personal information that we may hold about you and we may charge an administration fee.

**Information Security**

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal information that we have under our control from unauthorised access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification and unlawful destruction or accidental loss.

**Advertising And Interactive Website Services**

We accept advertisements and interactive areas of our website like our message boards enable website users to post personal information publicly and communicate with other website users. When your personal information is posted on our website publicly or you communicate with other users of our websites, other users of our website may collect your personal information.

**Links**

Our website contains links to third-party websites. If you access these links, you will leave our website. We do not control these other websites and their privacy practices may differ from ours.

**Privacy Support**

If you have a privacy related enquiry, you can write to us at webmaster [at] escortgps.xxx or use our Contact Form to contact us.

You acknowledge that by providing data to us, you consent to the processing of your data in accordance with this Privacy Statement.

We reserve the right to amend or modify this Privacy Statement at any time and in response to changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation.
